<resources>
    <string name="app_name">kweekmed</string>
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_account">Account</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="kweekmedlogo">kweekmedlogo</string>
    <string name="symptomscheckerlogo">symptomscheckerlogo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_patient_maps">Map</string>

    <!-- Edit Alarm Activity/Fragment -->
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="label">Label</string>
    <string name="days">Days</string>
    <string name="edit_alarm">Edit Alarm</string>
    <string name="add_alarm">Add Alarm</string>
    <string name="add_label_hint">Add a label!</string>
    <string name="update_complete">Changes Saved</string>
    <string name="update_failed">Update Failed</string>
    <string name="delete_complete">Alarm Deleted</string>
    <string name="delete_failed">Delete Failed</string>
    <string name="delete_dialog_title">Confirm Delete Alarm</string>
    <string name="delete_dialog_content">Are you sure you would like to delete this alarm?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <!-- Edit Alarm Menu -->
    <string name="action_save">Save</string>
    <string name="action_delete">Delete</string>

    <!-- Alarm Landing Page Activity/Fragment -->
    <string name="launch_main_activity">Launch Main Activity</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>

    <!-- Days -->
    <string name="monday">Monday</string>
    <string name="tuesday">Tuesday</string>
    <string name="wednesday">Wednesday</string>
    <string name="thursday">Thursday</string>
    <string name="friday">Friday</string>
    <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
    <string name="sunday">Sunday</string>

    <!-- Terms of use -->
    <string name="termsofuse">
        Terms Of Use:  PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. By using this site, you signify your assent to these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to all of these Terms and Conditions of use, do not use this App.! The Developers (MGC Empire Ltd.) may revise and update these Terms and Conditions at any time. Your continued usage of the KweekMed App.(“KweekMed App.,” or “KweekMed,” or the “App.,” or the “Application,”) will mean you accept those changes. V. KWEEKMED APP DOES NOT PROVIDE MEDICAL ADVICE The contents of the KweekMed App., such as text, graphics, images, informations obtained from verified third parties are for informational purposes only. The Content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on the KweekMed App.! If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or your local emergency number immediately. The KweekMed App does not recommend or endorse any specific tests, physicians, products, procedures, opinions, or other information that may be mentioned on the Site. Reliance on any information provided by KweekMed App., KweekMed employees, others appearing on the Site at the invitation of KweekMed, or other visitors to the Site is solely at your own risk. Under3ge Priv3cy We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. You should be aware that this App. is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 16. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is underage. Li3bility of KweekMed 3nd its Developers The use of the KweekMed App. and the Contents is at your own risk. When using the KweekMed App. information will be transmitted over a medium that may be beyond the control and jurisdiction of KweekMed and its Developers. Accordingly, KweekMed assumes no liability for or relating to the delay, failure, interruption, or corruption of any data or other information transmitted in connection with use of the KweekMed App. The KweekMed App. and the contents are provided on an "as is" basis. KWEEKMED, ITS DEVELOPERS, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTIES\ RIGHTS, AND FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE. Without limiting the foregoing, KweekMed, its Developers, make no representations or warranties about the following: The accuracy, reliability, completeness, currentness, or timeliness of the V. b. Content, software, text, graphics, links, or communications provided on or through the use of the KweekMed App. or KweekMed. The satisfaction of any government regulations requiring disclosure of information on prescription drug products or the approval or compliance of any software tools with regard to the Content contained on the KweekMed App. In no event shall KweekMed, its Developers, or any third parties mentioned on the KweekMed App. be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, incidental and consequential damages, personal injury/wrongful death, lost profits, or damages resulting from lost data or business interruption) resulting from the use of or inability to use the KweekMed App. or the Contents, whether based on warranty, contract, tort, or any other legal theory, and whether or not KweekMed, its Developers, or any third parties mentioned on the KweekMed App. are advised of the possibility of such damages. KweekMed, its Developers, or any third parties mentioned on the KweekMed App. are not liable for any personal injury, including death, caused by your use or misuse of the App., Content, or Public Areas. Advertisements, Se3rches, 3nd Links to Other Sites KweekMed may provide links to third-party web sites. KweekMed may agree to allow advertisers to display advertisements or sponsored content in the news area. KweekMed does not recommend and does not endorse the content on any thirdparty websites. KweekMed is not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites, sites framed within the KweekMed App., third-party sites, or third-party advertisements, and does not make any representations regarding their content or accuracy. Your use of third-party websites is at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use for such sites. KweekMed does not endorse any product, service, or treatment advertised on the KweekMed App. For more information, read our Advertising Policy. Indemnity You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold KweekMed, its officers, directors, employees, agents, Developers, harmless from and against any claims, actions or demands, liabilities and settlements including without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from, your violation of these Terms and Conditions. Except as expressly provided in a particular "legal notice" on the KweekMed App., these Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy constitute the entire agreement between you and KweekMed, the Developers, with respect to the use of the KweekMed App., and Content.
    </string>
    <!-- Private Policy -->
    <string name="privatepolicy">
        Privacy Policy: KweekMed, its Developers understands how important the privacy of personal information is to our users. This Privacy Policy with respect to the KweekMed apply to this App. and the services. If you do not want us to collect, use or disclose information about you and your use of the Services, then you should not use the Services. By using the Services, you must agree to the KweekMed Terms of Use, which is the contract between us and users of the Services.  By accepting the KweekMed Terms of Use, you confirm that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy and you acknowledge that we will store, use and otherwise process your information where we are located. References to “KweekMed,” “we” or “us” mean The Developers (MGC Empire Ltd.), including any company that The Developers controls (for example, a subsidiary of MGC Empire Ltd.). may share information among its subsidiaries or websites that it owns or controls, but information collected under this Privacy Policy is always protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy. Except as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy, MGC Empire Ltd. is the data controller responsible for the processing of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. Advertisement Policy : - (Add this under Priv3cy Policy in Settings) KweekMed accepts advertising on the KweekMed App. from third parties ("Advertisers"), which may include third party banners, badges, contextual advertising and content created or provided by an Advertiser (collectively referred to as "Advertisements" or "Advertising"). In addition, as used in this policy, the terms "Advertising" and "Advertisements" include third party banners, modules, links, microsites, native advertisements and other content provided by or on behalf of Advertisers. The Advertiser is responsible for the accuracy and objectivity of their Advertising. The following guidelines have been established by KweekMed to govern various aspects of Advertising on properties within the KweekMed App. The guidelines in this policy govern issues like acceptance of Advertisements by KweekMed, how Advertisements are displayed on the KweekMed App., and the removal of Advertisements from the KweekMed App. KweekMed has sole and absolute discretion with respect to interpretation and enforcement of this policy and all other issues associated with Advertising on the KweekMed App. KweekMed may change this policy at any time in its sole discretion by posting a revised policy to the applicable KweekMed Property. KweekMed has sole discretion for determining the types of Advertising that will be accepted and displayed on the KweekMed App., and under no circumstances will KweekMedʼs acceptance of any Advertisement be considered an endorsement of the product(s) and/or service(s) advertised or for the company that advertises, manufactures, distributes, or promotes the products or services. KweekMed will not knowingly accept Advertising that, in KweekMedʼs opinion, is not factually accurate and in good taste. There are certain categories of Advertisements that KweekMed will not knowingly permit on the KweekMed App. at any time. These categories include but are not limited to the following: Illegal, objectionable, ineffective and/or dangerous products (KweekMed reserves the right to determine what is objectionable, ineffective and/or dangerous) fraudulent, deceptive, illicit, misleading or offensive material material that misrepresents, ridicules, discriminates (real or implied) or attacks an individual or group on the basis of age, national origin, race, religion, gender, sexual orientation, marital status, disability or any other status deemed inappropriate for the KweekMed App. alcohol weapons, firearms, ammunition, or fireworks gambling pornography or related themes tobacco use of any kind the simulation of news or an emergency material that directly advertises products to or is intended to attract children under the age of 13 media or messages for or that reference "M" rated video games or content unreasonable, unlikely or extraordinary product or service claims media messages or imagery that strobe or flash media or messages that contain unsubstantiated "miracle" weight loss or other exaggerated claims of cure advertising units that mimic computer functions or deceptively indicate a computer or other function that would be reasonable to the average user to assume as a reason to click the unit KweekMed recognizes and maintains a distinct separation between  Advertising and KweekMedʼs editorial content. All Advertising on the KweekMed App. will be clearly and unambiguously identified. KweekMed will not allow any Advertising on the KweekMed App. that is not identified with the label of "Advertisement", "From Our Advertiser", "Information From Industry" or a similar designation indicating that the Advertising is being provided by or on behalf of an Advertiser. A click on an Advertisement may only link the end user to the Advertisers site or to relevant sponsored content area. KweekMed reserves the right to decide at any time in its sole discretion whether it will accept, reject, cancel, or remove Advertising from the KweekMed App. KweekMed cannot provide any assurances that Advertisements will perform without error on all platforms. It is the Advertisers responsibility to comply with all domestic and foreign laws and regulations applicable to its Advertising within the KweekMed App (and to include all legally required legends, disclosures and statements in such Advertising), including without limitation the current FDA guidelines for Direct to Physician (DTP) and Direct to Consumer (DTC) advertising. WebMD will not monitor compliance with such laws and regulations. However, KweekMed reserves the right to review all Advertising for compliance with applicable laws and regulations and, if KweekMed becomes aware of any breach or potential breach of any applicable law or regulation or of these guidelines, KweekMed may remove the Advertising from the KweekMed App. No Advertising on the KweekMed App. shall include any pixels, tags, flash containers or any other type of information collection software code (any such pixel, tag, code or device a "Pixel") or shall place any beacons, cookies or other information collection devices on the browsers of users of the KweekMed App. unless expressly approved in writing by KweekMed. If KweekMed approves the inclusion of a Pixel in an advertisement, then unless and only to the extent that such approval contains an express exception, (i) Advertiser may not use such Pixel to collect any personally-identifiable information (PII) with respect to any KweekMed user, (ii) no such Pixel can be flash or object based, (iii) the Pixel can be blocked and any cookie placed can be deleted by user browser settings, (iv) Advertiser will not link any non-PII that it collects to any PII that it may have from any other source and (v) Advertiser will not update any existing profile or create any profile in its database based on any data collected on the KweekMed App., including the fact that someone is a KweekMed user or any information derived from the information in the referring URL. References to “KweekMed,” “we” or “us” mean The Developers (MGC Empire Ltd.), including any company that The Developers controls (for example, a subsidiary of MGC Empire Ltd.).
    </string>
    <!-- About KWeekmed -->
    <string name="aboutkweekmed">
        About KweekMed: We are a source for original and timely health information as well as material from verified third parties and also direct contact to health physicians around your location so getting treatment doesnʼt have to be so much stress. Our team at KweekMed is dedicated to helping people find the health and medical information, support, and services they need as soon as they need it. We are dedicated to providing quality health information and to upholding the integrity of our process. As serious as we are about credibility, we also know that at times, health information can and should be engaging, exciting, and entertaining. We pride ourselves in knowing what our audience needs and delivering the most appropriate experience. Our mission is to fulfill all these needs in the most appropriate ways possible. We are committed to improving our Services. We will continue to publish even more content, communities, and services to help make your life better, to help you find your way when faced with healthcare decisions, and to help you feel better about your health and that of your family.
    </string>
    <!--About the developers -->
    <string name="aboutthedevelopers">
        MGC Empire Limited is an IT company with our headquarters located in Lagos, Nigeria. We specialize in mobile app development for both Android and IOS devices. We also offer IT Services to both Individual and Corporate customers.
    </string>
    <!--Note for Doctors During SignUp -->
    <string name="notesfordoctors">
        Please if you are a doctor, Your account needs to be verified by the admin. Kindly email a scanned copy of your medical certificate to kweekmed@kweekmed.mgcempire.comand we would tell you the next steps on how to be a verified doctor on our medical platform
    </string>


    <!-- For heartrate monitor -->
    <string name="default_text">--</string>


    <string name="HowToUse">
        <b>Symptoms Checker:</b>\nClick on the symptoms checker icon on the home page, input your age and gender, select your symptoms by ticking on the boxes on the right and kweekmed would give you a list of the possible conditions you might be facing with a bar that shows how accurate the prediction is(always remember that kweekmed results are only predictions, please contact a trained professional for full body check if the need arises. \n <b>Possible Conditions:</b>\nClick on the Possible Conditions Icon on the home page to see a complete list of all the conditions any human could have. \n <b>Drugs and Medications:</b>\nClick on the Drugs and medications Icon to open a database of over 65,000 drugs used world wide. You can also use this to identify medicines if you have the right parameters <b>NOTE:</b> kweekmed does not won or control pillbox, kweekmed has only linked to this site and charges no fee whatsoever for the use of this service. \n <b>Medication Reminders:</b>\nClick on the Medication Reminder Icon to create reminders/alarms for medical purposes. \n<b>Find a Doctor:</b>\nClick on the find a doctor icon to view a list of all kweekmed registered doctors. All doctors on this list are arranged according to how far the doctors are away from you. <b>NOTE:</b> All the doctors registered on our platform are professionals and have reasonable years of experience. We have scrutinized all our doctors to be sure that you get the best medical advice and treatments \n <b>Blood Pressure Checker:</b>\nTo Use the heartrate monitor, Open the by tapping on the heart rate monitor icon on the homepage: Place your finger between your camera and the flash but do not apply too much pressure. This app uses the flash and camera to feel the pulse of your finger and get a very near accurate heart beat rate. 
    </string>

    <!-- default profile picture image link -->
    <string name="DEFAULT_PROFILE_PICTURE_LINK">https://res.cloudinary.com/the-software-gurus-place/image/upload/v1540382277/kweekmed/profilepictures/noprofilepicture.png</string>

</resources>
